

# Vedran Olujić

Address: Ulica Nike Grškovića 58, Zagreb, Croatia

e-mail: vedranolujic23@gmail.com

**Contact number:** +385-95-198-9904

### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

MSc of electrical engineering & information technology with a demonstrated history in the software development industry. Experienced in software development and all major software lifecycle methodologies. Diverse technical background and skills in all aspects of software testing with a focus on embedded systems. Also interested in embedded engineering, acoustics, and audio electronics.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# dSPACE Engineering d.o.o.

Zagreb, Croatia

Software test engineer

August 2019 - present

• Software testing of dSPACE RCP and HIL and FlexRay configuration tool. Test case execution and analysis. Manual testing, test framework improvements and refactoring, test case design, testing documentation, mentoring newcomers. Technologies used: MATLAB/Simulink, Python, C, C#.

# Ericsson Nikola Tesla d.d.

Zagreb, Croatia

Software developer

October 2017 – July 2019

Software development intern

November 2016 – October 2017

• Cross functional software development and quality assurance in the radio software department. Replaced an old Perl based automatic test system with a faster, more efficient testNG system. Executed and planned continuous verification with constant test methodology and strategy improvement. Developed and tested Ericsson Spectrum Sharing feature, enabling 5G-NR carriers on legacy radios and frequency bands.

# GlobalLogic d.d.

Software development internship

Zagreb, Croatia July - August 2016

• Embedded C software development for ARM Cortex-M4 processors on STM32F4 development boards. Development of a home automation system.

Cei-ieta d.o.o.

Zagreb, Croatia

Internship in a metrology laboratory

February - March 2016

• Translation of an oscilloscope calibration guide from English to Croatian language, calibration of various electronic devices and electrical components.

### Ericsson Nikola Tesla Servisi d.o.o.

Zagreb, Croatia

Dispatcher

July - August 2015

• Dispatching and support for radio base station field technicians

### **EDUCATION**

# MSc of electrical engineering and information technology

10/2015 -7/2017

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing

- Profile: Electronic and Computer Engineering
- Master thesis: "Digitally Controlled System for Audio Input and Output

Selection in Control Rooms"

# BSc of electrical engineering and information technology

9/2010 - 7/2015

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing

- Profile: Electronics
- Bachelor thesis: "Microphone Preamplifier"

## Frank W. Cox High School (advanced diploma)

9/2007 - 6/2010

Virginia Beach, Virginia, United States

• Principal's List: 4.0 GPA student

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

# **Programming languages:**

- C
- C#
- Python
- MATLAB

**Technologies used:** Git, PTC Integrity, Gerrit, Linux, JSON, XML, Java, PyCharm, TestNG, Eclipse, Jenkins, Microsoft Office, Logic Pro, Keil, JIRA, Altium Designer, EASE, ARTA, MATLAB/Simulink, dSPACE RCP and HIL, Vector CANalyzer, Ranorex

## LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

**ISTQB Foundation Level:** ISTQB - International Software Testing Qualifications Board, issued November 2019.

C# Intermediate - Classes Interfaces and OOP: Udemy, issued March 2020.

## **OTHER SKILLS**

Native language: Croatian

Second languages: English C1, German A2

Driver's license: category B

Hobbies and interests: DIY electronics, Audio engineering, Guitar, Arduino, IoT